(Raj:)How are you gonna get
James Earl Jones?
(Sheldon:)Simple. Earlier today, he Tweeted
that he's looking forward
(Sheldon:)to going to his favourite
sushi restaurant for dinner.
(Sheldon:)I Googled an interview
from four years ago
(Sheldon:)which was conducted in
his favourite sushi restaurant.
(Sheldon:)That's where he'll be,
and that's where I'm going, and--
(Howard:)And that's where Darth Vader's gonna
pour soy sauce on your head.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I don't care if you get
scalped tickets with us or not,
(Leonard:)but please don't be creepy
and go stalking this poor guy.
(Leonard:)You're gonna get in trouble.
(Sheldon:)You're the ones
who are going to get in trouble.
(Sheldon:)You're buying
non-transferable tickets.
(Sheldon:)And from a stranger, no less.
(Sheldon:)Not only can you get
banned from Comic-Con,
(Sheldon:)if caught, you could be charged
with petty theft.
(Sheldon:)You think about that while
I'm warning James Earl Jones
(Sheldon:)about the danger of posting
his location on Twitter.
(Sheldon:)He got lucky this time.
There are some weirdos out there.